// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: " When did the New Year’s Eve Ball first drop in Times Square?",
      answer: "1907",
      options: [
        "1907",
        "1902",
        "1908",
        "1912"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "How large is the Times Square New Year’s Eve Ball in diameter?",
      answer: "12 feet",
      options: [
        "10 feet",
        "08 feet",
        "12 feet",
        "14 feet"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "When did partiers first celebrate New Year’s Eve in Times Square?",
      answer: "1904",
      options: [
        "1904",
        "1906",
        "1908",
        "1910"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: " How many versions of the Times Square New Year’s Eve Ball have there been to date?",
      answer: "Seven",
      options: [
        "Five",
        "Six",
        "Seven",
        "Eight"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "How much did the first Times Square New Year’s Eve Ball weigh?",
      answer: "700 Pounds",
      options: [
        "550 Pounds",
        "600 Pounds",
        "650 Pounds",
        "700 Pounds"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "How many light bulbs covered the first Times Square New Year’s Eve Ball?",
      answer: "100",
      options: [
        "90",
        "95",
        "100",
        "105"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "When did LED lights first appear on the Times Square New Year’s Eve Ball?",
      answer: "2007",
      options: [
        "2006",
        "2007",
        "2009",
        "2010"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "How many LED modules are in the Times Square New Year’s Eve Ball?",
      answer: " 672",
      options: [
        "680",
        "676",
        "672",
        "670"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "How many triangles total are there on the Times Square ball?",
      answer: "2688",
      options: [
        "2658",
        "2668",
        "2678",
        "2688"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "How many colors can the Times Square New Year’s Eve Ball display?",
      answer: "16 Million",
      options: [
        "14 Millon",
        "15 Million",
        "16 Million",
        "17 Million"
      ]
    },
  ];